Inventory of the Frank and Doris Hursely papers, 1942-1969
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
- Radio Scripts
  - Service to the Front
    - November 21, 1944 (Box 34)
    - November 28, 1944 (Box 35)
    - December 5, 1944 (Box 35)
    - December 12, 1944 (Box 35)
    - December 19, 1944 (Box 35)
    - December 26, 1944 (Box 35)
    - January 2, 1945 (Box 35)
    - January 9, 1945 (Box 35)
    - January 16, 1945 (Box 35)
    - January 23, 1945 (Box 35)
    - January 30, 1945 (Box 35)
    - February 6, 1945 (Box 35)
    - February 13, 1945 (Box 35)
    - February 20, 1945 (Box 35)
    - February 22, 1945 (Box 35)
    - March 6, 1945 (Box 35)
    - March 13, 1945 (Box 36)
    - March 20, 1945 (Box 36)
    - March 27, 1945 (Box 36)
    - April 3, 1945 (Box 36)
    - April 10, 1945 (Box 36)
    - April 17, 1945 (Box 36)
    - May 1, 1945 (Box 36)
    - May 8, 1945 (Box 36)
    - May 15, 1945 (Box 36)
    - May 22, 1945 (Box 36)
    - May 29, 1945 (Box 36)
    - June 12, 1945 (Box 36)
    - June 19, 1945 (Box 36)
    - June 26, 1945 (Box 36)
    - July 3, 1945 (Box 37)
    - July 10, 1945 (Box 37)
    - July 17, 1945 (Box 37)
    - July 24, 1945 (Box 37)
    - July 21, 1945 (Box 37)
    - August 7, 1945 (Box 37)
    - August 14, 1945 (Box 37)
    - August 21, 1945 (Box 37)
    - August 28, 1945 (Box 37)
  - That's Rich
    - January 8, 1954 (Box 37)
    - January 15, 1954 (Box 37)
    - January 22, 1954 (Box 37)
    - January 29, 1954 (Box 37)
    - February 5, 1954 (Box 37)
    - February 12, 1954 (Box 38)
    - February 19, 1954 (Box 38)
    - February 26, 1954 (Box 38)
    - March 5, 1954 (Box 38)
    - March 6, 1954 (Box 38)
    - March 13, 1954 (Box 38)
    - March 26, 1954 (Box 38)
    - April 2, 1954 (Box 38)
    - April 9, 1954 (Box 38)
    - April 16, 1954 (Box 38)
    - April 23, 1954 (Box 38)
    - April 30, 1954 (Box 38)
    - May 7, 1954 (Box 38)
    - May 21, 1954 (Box 38)
    - May 29, 1954 (Box 38)
    - May 21, 1954 (Box 39)
    - May 22, 1954 (Box 39)
    - May 23, 1954 (Box 39)
    - May 27, 1954 (Box 39)
    - May 27, 1954 (Box 39)
    - Auditions (Box 39)
    - Story Lines (Box 39)
    - Television Scripts (Box 39)
  - The Truitts
    - February 20, 1950 (Box 40)
    - February 27, 1950 (Box 40)
    - March 11, 1950 (Box 40)
    - March 23, 1950 (Box 40)
    - April 8, 1950 (Box 40)
    - May 13, 1950 (Box 40)
    - May 20, 1950 (Box 40)
    - May 27, 1950 (Box 40)
    - June 3, 1950 (Box 41)
    - June 10, 1950 (Box 41)
    - June 17, 1950 (Box 41)
    - June 24, 1950 (Box 41)
    - July 1, 1950 (Box 41)
    - July 8, 1950 (Box 42)
    - July 15, 1950 (Box 42)
    - July 22, 1950 (Box 42)
    - September 23, 1950 (Box 42)
    - November 11, 1950 (Box 42)
    - November 17, 1950 (Box 42)
    - November 24, 1950 (Box 42)
    - July 7, 1951 (Box 43)
    - July 14, 1951 (Box 43)
    - August 18, 1951 (Box 43)
    - Auditions (Box 43)
    - Spots (Box 43)
  - The Websters
    - March 3, 1946 (Box 44)
    - March 10, 1946 (Box 44)
    - March 17, 1946 (Box 44)
    - March 24, 1946 (Box 44)
    - March 31, 1946 (Box 44)
    - April 7, 1946 (Box 44)
    - April 14, 1946 (Box 44)
    - April 21, 1946 (Box 4)
    - April 28, 1946 (Box 44)
    - May 5, 1946 (Box 44)
    - May 12, 1946 (Box 44)
    - May 19, 1946 (Box 44)
    - May 26, 1946 (Box 44)
    - June 2, 1946 (Box 44)
    - June 9, 1946 (Box 45)
    - June 16, 1946 (Box 45)
    - June 23, 1946 (Box 45)
    - June 30, 1946 (Box 45)
    - July 7, 1946 (Box 45)
    - July 14, 1946 (Box 45)
    - July 28, 1946 (Box 45)
    - August 4, 1946 (Box 45)
    - August 11, 1946 (Box 45)
    - August 13, 1946 (Box 45)
    - August 25, 1946 (Box 45)
    - September 1, 1946 (Box 45)
    - September 8, 1946 (Box 45)
    - September 15, 1946 (Box 45)
    - September 22, 1946 (Box 45)
    - September 29, 1946 (Box 45)
    - October 6, 1946 (Box 46)
    - October 13, 1946 (Box 46)
    - October 20, 1946 (Box 46)
    - October 27, 1946 (Box 46)
    - November 3, 1946 (Box 46)
    - November 10, 1946 (Box 46)
    - November 17, 1946 (Box 46)
    - November 24, 1946 (Box 46)
    - December 1, 1946 (Box 46)
    - December 8, 1946 (Box 46)
    - December 15, 1946 (Box 46)
    - December 22, 1946 (Box 46)
    - December 29, 1946 (Box 46)
    - January 5, 1947 (Box 46)
    - January 12, 1947 (Box 46)
    - January 19, 1947 (Box 47)
    - January 26, 1947 (Box 47)
    - February 2, 1947 (Box 47)
    - February 9, 1947 (Box 47)
    - February 16, 1947 (Box 47)
    - February 23, 1947 (Box 47)
    - March 2, 1947 (Box 47)
    - March 9, 1947 (Box 47)
    - March 16, 1947 (Box 47)
    - March 23, 1947 (Box 47)
    - March 30, 1947 (Box 47)
    - April 6, 1947 (Box 48)
    - April 13, 1947 (Box 48)
    - April 20, 1947 (Box 48)
    - April 27, 1947 (Box 48)
    - May 4, 1947 (Box 48)
    - May 11, 1947 (Box 48)
    - May 18, 1947 (Box 48)
    - May 25, 1947 (Box 48)
    - June 1, 1947 (Box 48)
    - June 8, 1947 (Box 48)
    - June 15, 1947 (Box 49)
    - June 22, 1947 (Box 49)
    - June 29, 1947 (Box 49)
    - July 6, 1947 (Box 49)
    - July 13, 1947 (Box 49)
    - July 20, 1947 (Box 49)
    - July 27, 1947 (Box 49)
    - August 3, 1947 (Box 49)
    - August 10, 1947 (Box 49)
    - August 17, 1947 (Box 49)
    - August 24, 1947 (Box 49)
    - August 31, 1947 (Box 49)
    - September 7, 1947 (Box 50)
    - September 14, 1947 (Box 50)
    - September 21, 1947 (Box 50)
    - September 28, 1947 (Box 50)
    - October 5, 1947 (Box 50)
    - October 12, 1947 (Box 50)
    - October 19, 1947 (Box 50)
    - October 26, 1947 (Box 50)
    - November 2, 1947 (Box 50)
    - November 9, 1947 (Box 50)
    - November 16, 1947 (Box 51)
    - November 23, 1947 (Box 51)
    - November 30, 1947 (Box 51)
    - November 30, 1947 (Box 51)
    - December 14, 1947 (Box 51)
    - December 21, 1947 (Box 51)
    - December 28, 1947 (Box 51)
    - January 4, 1948 (Box 51)
    - January 11, 1948 (Box 51)
    - January 18, 1948 (Box 51)
    - January 25, 1948 (Box 51)
    - February 1, 1948 (Box 52)
    - February 8, 1948 (Box 52)
    - February 15, 1948 (Box 52)
    - February 22, 1948 (Box 52)
    - February 29, 1948 (Box 52)
    - March 7, 1948 (Box 52)
    - March 14, 1948 (Box 52)
    - March 21, 1948 (Box 52)
    - March 28, 1948 (Box 52)
    - April 4, 1948 (Box 52)
    - April 11, 1948 (Box 53)
    - April 18, 1948 (Box 53)
    - April 25, 1948 (Box 53)
    - May 2, 1948 (Box 53)
    - May 9, 1948 (Box 53)
    - May 16, 1948 (Box 53)
    - May 23, 1948 (Box 53)
    - May 30, 1948 (Box 53)
    - June 6, 1948 (Box 53)
    - June 13, 1948 (Box 54)
    - June 20, 1948 (Box 54)
    - June 27, 1948 (Box 54)
    - July 4, 1948 (Box 54)
    - July 11, 1948 (Box 54)
    - July 18, 1948 (Box 54)
    - July 25, 1948 (Box 54)
    - August 1, 1948 (Box 54)
    - August 8, 1948 (Box 54)
    - August 15, 1948 (Box 55)
    - August 22, 1948 (Box 55)
- Television Scripts
  - General Hospital
    - March 29 to April 2, 1965 (Box 55)
      Week #61-65
    - April 5-9, 1965 (Box 55)
      Week #66-70
    - April 12-16, 1965 (Box 55)
      Week #71-75
    - April 19-23, 1965 (Box 55)
      Week #76-80
    - April 26-30, 1965 (Box 56)
      Week #81-85
    - May 3-7, 1965 (Box 56)
      Week #86-90
    - May 10-14, 1965 (Box 56)
      Week #91-95
    - May 17-21, 1965 (Box 56)
      Week #16-100
    - May 24-28, 1965 (Box 56)
      Week #101-105
    - May 31 to June 4, 1965 (Box 56)
      Week #106-110
    - June 7-11, 1965 (Box 57)
      Week #111-115
    - June 14-18, 1965 (Box 57)
      Week #116-120
    - June 21-25, 1965 (Box 57)
      Week #121-125
    - June 28 to July 2, 1965 (Box 57)
      Week #126-130
    - July 6-9, 1965 (Box 57)
      Week #131-135
    - July 12-16, 1965 (Box 57)
      Week #136-140
    - July 19-23, 1965 (Box 58)
      Week #141-145
    - July 26-30, 1965 (Box 58)
      Week #146-150
    - August 2-6, 1965 (Box 58)
      Week #151-155
    - August 8-13, 1965 (Box 58)
      Week #156-160
    - August 16-20, 1965 (Box 58)
      Week #161-165
    - August 23-27, 1965 (Box 58)
      Week #166-170
    - August 30 to September 3, 1965 (Box 59)
      Week #171-175
    - September 6-10, 1965 (Box 59)
      Week #176-180
    - September 13-17, 1965 (Box 59)
      Week #181-185
    - September 20-24, 1965 (Box 59)
      Week #186-190
    - September 27 to October 1, 1965 (Box 59)
      Week #191-195
    - October 4-8, 1965 (Box 59)
      Week #196-200
    - October 11-15, 1965 (Box 60)
      Week #201-205
    - October 18-22, 1965 (Box 60)
      Week #206-210
    - October 25-29, 1965 (Box 60)
      Week #211-215
    - November 1-5, 1965 (Box 60)
      Week #216-220
    - November 8-12, 1965 (Box 60)
      Week #221-225
    - November 15-19, 1965 (Box 60)
      Week #226-230
    - November 22-26, 1965 (Box 61)
      Week #231-235
    - November 29 to December 3, 1965 (Box 61)
      Week #236-240
    - December 6-10, 1965 (Box 61)
      Week #241-245
    - December 13-17, 1965 (Box 61)
      Week #246-250
    - December 20-24, 1965 (Box 61)
      Week #251-255
    - December 27-30, 1965 (Box 61)
      Week #256-259
    - January 3-7, 1966 (Box 62)
      Week #1-5
    - January 1-14, 1966 (Box 62)
      Week #6-10
    - January 17-21, 1966 (Box 62)
      Week #11-15
    - January 24-20, 1966 (Box 62)
      Week #16-20
    - January 31 to February 4, 1966 (Box 62)
      Week #21-25
    - February 7-11, 1966 (Box 62)
      Week #26-30
    - February 14-18, 1966 (Box 62)
      Week #31-35
    - February 21-25, 1966 (Box 63)
      Week #36-40
    - February 28 to March44, 1966 (Box 63)
      Week #41-45
    - March 7-11, 1966 (Box 63)
      Week #46-50
    - March 14-18, 1966 (Box 63)
      Week #51-55
    - March 21-25, 1966 (Box 63)
      Week #56-60
    - March 28 to April 1, 1966 (Box 63)
    - April 4-8, 1966 (Box 63)
    - April 11-15, 1966 (Box 64)
    - April 18-22, 1966 (Box 64)
    - April 25-29, 1966 (Box 64)
    - May 2-6, 1966 (Box 64)
    - May 9-13, 1966 (Box 64)
    - May 16-20, 1966 (Box 64)
      Week #96-100
    - May 23-27, 1966 (Box 64)
    - May 30 to June 2, 1966 (Box 65)
    - June 6-10, 1966 (Box 65)
    - June 13-17, 1966 (Box 65)
    - June 20-24, 1966 (Box 65)
    - June 27 to July 1, 1966 (Box 65)
    - July 4-8, 1966 (Box 65)
    - July 11-15, 1966 (Box 66)
    - July 18-22, 1965 (Box 66)
    - July 25-29, 1966 (Box 66)
    - August 1-5, 1966 (Box 66)
    - August 8-12, 1966 (Box 66)
    - August 15-19, 1966 (Box 66)
    - August 22-26, 1966 (Box 67)
    - August 26 to September 2, 1966 (Box 67)
    - September 5-9, 1966 (Box 67)
    - September 12-16, 1966 (Box 67)
    - September 18-20, 1966 (Box 67)
    - September 26-30, 1966 (Box 67)
    - October 2-7, 1966 (Box 67)
    - October 10-14, 1966 (Box 68)
    - October 17-21, 1966 (Box 68)
    - October 24-28, 1966 (Box 68)
    - October 31 to November 4, 1966 (Box 68)
    - November 7-11, 1966 (Box 68)
    - November 14-18, 1966 (Box 68)
    - November 21-23, 1966 (Box 68)
    - November 30 to December 2, 1966 (Box 69)
      Week #238-240
    - December 5-9, 1966 (Box 69)
    - December 12-16, 1966 (Box 69)
    - December 19-23, 1966 (Box 69)
    - December 26-30, 1966 (Box 69)
      Week #256-260
    - January 2-6, 1967 (Box 69)
    - January 9-13, 1967 (Box 69)
    - January 16-20, 1967 (Box 70)
    - January 23-27, 1967 (Box 70)
    - January 30 to February 3, 1967 (Box 70)
    - February 6-10, 1967 (Box 70)
    - February 13-17, 1967 (Box 70)
    - February 20-24, 1967 (Box 70)
    - February 27 to March 3, 1967 (Box 71)
    - March 6-10, 1967 (Box 71)
    - March 13-17, 1967 (Box 71)
    - March 20-24, 1967 (Box 72)
    - March 27-31, 1967 (Box 72)
    - April 11-14, 1967 (Box 72)
      Week #66-67, 74 & 75
    - April 17-21, 1967 (Box 73)
    - April 24-28, 1967 (Box 73)
    - May 1-5, 1967 (Box 73)
    - May 8-12, 1967 (Box 73)
    - May 15-19, 1967 (Box 74)
    - May 22-26, 1967 (Box 74)
    - May 29 to June 2, 1967 (Box 74)
    - June 5-9, 1967 (Box 75)
    - June 12-16, 1967 (Box 75)
    - June 19-23, 1967 (Box 75)
    - June 26-30, 1967 (Box 76)
    - July 3-7, 1967 (Box 76)
    - July 10-14, 1967 (Box 76)
    - July 17-21, 1967 (Box 76)
    - July 24-28, 1967 (Box 77)
    - July 31 to August 4, 1967 (Box 77)
    - August 7-11, 1967 (Box 77)
    - August 14-18, 1967 (Box 78)
    - August 21-25, 1967 (Box 78)
    - August 28 to September 1, 1967 (Box 78)
    - September 4-9, 1967 (Box 78)
    - September 11-15, 1967 (Box 79)
    - September 18-22, 1967 (Box 79)
    - September 25-29, 1967 (Box 79)
    - October 2-6, 1967 (Box 80)
    - October 16-20, 1967 (Box 80)
    - October 23-27, 1967 (Box 80)
    - October 30 to November 3, 1967 (Box 81)
    - November 6-10, 1967 (Box 81)
    - November 13-17, 1967 (Box 81)
    - November 20-24, 1967 (Box 82)
    - November 27 to December 1, 1967 (Box 82)
    - December 4-8, 1967 (Box 82)
    - December 11-15, 1967 (Box 82)
    - December 18-22, 1967 (Box 83)
    - December 26-29, 1967 (Box 83)
    - January 1-5, 1968 (Box 83)
    - January 8-12, 1968 (Box 84)
    - January 15-19, 1968 (Box 84)
    - January 22-26, 1968 (Box 84)
    - January 29 to February 2, 1968 (Box 85)
    - February 5-9, 1968 (Box 85)
    - February 12-16, 1968 (Box 85)
    - February 19-23, 1968 (Box 86)
    - February 26-to March 1, 1968 (Box 86)
    - March 4-8, 1968 (Box 86)
    - March 11-15, 1968 (Box 87)
    - March 18-22, 1968 (Box 87)
    - March 25-29, 1968 (Box 87)
    - April 1-5, 1968 (Box 88)
    - April 8-12, 1968 (Box 88)
    - April 15-19, 1968 (Box 88)
    - April 22-26, 1968 (Box 88)
    - April 30 to May 3, 1968 (Box 89)
    - May 6-10, 1968 (Box 89)
    - May 13-17, 1968 (Box 89)
    - May 29-24, 1968 (Box 90)
    - May 27-31, 1968 (Box 90)
    - June 3-7, 1968 (Box 90)
    - June 10-14, 1968 (Box 90)
    - June 17-21, 1968 (Box 91)
    - June 24-28, 1968 (Box 91)
    - July 1-5, 1968 (Box 91)
    - July 8-12, 1968 (Box 92)
    - July 15-19, 1968 (Box 92)
    - July 22-26, 1968 (Box 92)
    - July 29 to August 2, 1968 (Box 93)
    - August 5-9, 1968 (Box 93)
    - August 12-16, 1968 (Box 93)
    - August 19-23, 1968 (Box 94)
    - August 26-30, 1968 (Box 94)
    - September 2-6, 1968 (Box 94)
    - September 9-13, 1968 (Box 95)
    - September 16-20, 1968 (Box 95)
    - September 23-27, 1968 (Box 96)
    - September 30 to October 4, 1968 (Box 96)
    - October 7-10, 1968 (Box 96)
    - October 14-18, 1968 (Box 97)
    - October 21-25, 1968 (Box 97)
    - October 28 to November 1, 1968 (Box 98)
    - November 4-8, 1968 (Box 98)
    - November 11-15, 1968 (Box 98)
    - November 18-22, 1968 (Box 99)
    - November 25-29, 1968 (Box 99)
      Week #235-240
    - December 2-6,1968 (Box 99)
    - December 9-13, 1968 (Box 100)
    - December 16-20, 1968 (Box 100)
    - December 23-27, 1968 (Box 100)
    - December 30-31, 1968 (Box 101)
      Week #261-262
    - January 1-3, 1969 (Box 101)
      Week #3-5
    - January 6-10, 1969 (Box 101)
    - January 13-17, 1969 (Box 101)
    - January 20-24, 1969 (Box 102)
    - January 27-31, 1969 (Box 102)
    - February 3-7, 1969 (Box 102)
    - February 10-14, 1969 (Box 103)
    - February 17-21, 1969 (Box 103)
    - February 24-28, 1969 (Box 104)
    - March 3-7, 1969 (Box 104)
    - March 10-14, 1969 (Box 105)
    - March 17-21, 1969 (Box 105)
    - March 24-28, 1969 (Box 106)
  - Search For Tomorrow
    - December 30-31, 1957 (Box 106)
      Week #1651-1652
    - January 1-10, 1958 (Box 106)
      Week #1653-1655
    - January 6-10, 1958 (Box 106)
      Week #1656-1660
    - January 13-17, 1958 (Box 106)
      Week #1661-1665
    - January 20-24, 1958 (Box 106)
      Week #1666-1670
    - January 27-31, 1958 (Box 106)
      Week #1671-1675
    - February 3-7, 1958 (Box 106)
      Week #1676-1680
    - February 10-14, 1958 (Box 107)
      Week #1681-1685
    - February 17-21, 1958 (Box 107)
      Week #1686-1690
    - February 24-28, 1958 (Box 107)
      Week #1691-1695
    - March 3-7, 1958 (Box 107)
      Week #1696-1700
    - March 10-14, 1958 (Box 107)
      Week #1701-1705
    - March 17-21, 1958 (Box 107)
      Week #1706-1710
    - March 24-28, 1958 (Box 107)
      Week #1711-1715
    - March 31 to April 4, 1958 (Box 107)
      Week #1716-1720
    - April 7-11, 1958 (Box 107)
      Week #1721-1725
    - April 14-18, 1958 (Box 107)
      Week #1726-1730
    - April 21-25, 1958 (Box 108)
      Week #1731-1735
    - April 28 to May 2, 1958 (Box 108)
      Week #1736-1740
    - May 5-9, 1958 (Box 108)
      Week #1741-1745
    - May 12-16, 1958 (Box 108)
      Week #1746-1750
    - May 19-23, 1958 (Box 108)
      Week #1751-1755
    - May 26-30, 1958 (Box 108)
      Week #1756-1760
    - June 2-6, 1958 (Box 108)
      Week #1761-1765
    - June 9-13, 1958 (Box 108)
      Week #1766-1770
    - June 16-20, 1958 (Box 108)
      Week #1771-1775
    - June 23-27, 1958 (Box 108)
      Week #1776-1780
    - June 30 to July 4, 1958 (Box 109)
      Week #1781-1785
    - July 7-11, 1958 (Box 109)
      Week #1786-1790
    - July 14-18, 1958 (Box 109)
      Week #1791-1795
    - July 21-25, 1958 (Box 109)
      Week #1796-1800
    - July 28 to August 1, 1958 (Box 109)
      Week #1801-1805
    - August 4-8, 1958 (Box 109)
      Week #1806-1810
    - August 11-15, 1958 (Box 109)
      Week #1811-1815
    - August 18-22, 1958 (Box 109)
      Week #1816-1820
    - August 25-29, 1958 (Box 109)
      Week #1821-1825
    - September 1-5, 1958 (Box 109)
      Week #1826-1830
    - September 8-12, 1958 (Box 110)
    - September 15-19, 1958 (Box 110)
      Week #1821-1835
    - September 22-26, 1958 (Box 110)
      Week #1836-1840
    - September 29 to October 3, 1958 (Box 110)
      Week #1841-1845
    - October 6-10, 1958 (Box 110)
      Week #1846-1850
    - October 13-17, 1958 (Box 110)
      Week #1851-1855
    - October 20-24, 1958 (Box 110)
      Week #1856-1860
    - October 27-31, 1958 (Box 110)
      Week #1861-1865
    - November 3-7, 1958 (Box 110)
      Week #1866-1870
    - November 10-14, 1958 (Box 110)
      Week #1871-1875
    - November 17-21, 1958 (Box 110)
      Week #1876-1880
    - November 24-28, 1958 (Box 111)
      Week #1881-1885
    - December 1-5, 1958 (Box 111)
      Week #1886-1890
    - December 8-12, 1958 (Box 111)
      Week #1891-1895
    - December 15-19, 1958 (Box 111)
      Week #1896-1900
    - December 22-26, 1958 (Box 111)
      Week #1901-1905
    - December 29-31, 1958 (Box 111)
      Week #1906-1908
    - January 1-2, 1959 (Box 111)
      Week #1909-1910
    - January 5-9, 1959 (Box 111)
      Week #1911-1915
    - January 12-16, 1959 (Box 111)
      Week #1916-1920
    - January 19-23, 1959 (Box 111)
      Week #1921-1925
    - January 26-30, 1959 (Box 111)
      Week #1926-1930
    - February 2-6, 1959 (Box 112)
      Week #1931-1935
    - February 9-13, 1959 (Box 112)
      Week #1936-1940
    - February 16-20, 1959 (Box 112)
      Week #1941-1945
    - February 23-27, 1959 (Box 112)
      Week #1946-1950
    - March 2-6, 1959 (Box 112)
      Week #1951-1955
    - March 8-13, 1959 (Box 112)
      Week #1956-1960
    - March 16-20, 1959 (Box 112)
      Week #1961-1965
    - March 23-27, 1959 (Box 112)
      Week #1966-1970
    - March 30-to April 3, 1959 (Box 112)
      Week #1971-1975
    - April 6-10, 1959 (Box 112)
      Week #1976-1980
    - April 13-17, 1959 (Box 112)
      Week #1981-1985
    - April 20-24, 1959 (Box 113)
      Week #1986-1990
    - April 27-to May 1, 1959 (Box 113)
      Week #1991-1995
    - May 4-8, 1959 (Box 113)
      Week #1996-2000
    - May 11-15, 1959 (Box 113)
      Week #2001-2005
    - May 16-22, 1959 (Box 113)
      Week #2006-2010
    - May 25-29, 1959 (Box 113)
      Week #2011-2015
    - June 1-5, 1959 (Box 113)
      Week #2016-2020
    - June 8-12, 1959 (Box 113)
      Week #2021-2025
    - June 15-19, 1959 (Box 113)
      Week #2026-2030
    - June 22-26, 1959 (Box 113)
      Week #2031-2035
    - June 29 to July 3, 1959 (Box 113)
      Week #2036-2040
    - July 6-10, 1959 (Box 114)
      Week #2041-2045
    - July 13-17, 1959 (Box 114)
      Week #2046-2050
    - July 20-24, 1959 (Box 114)
      Week #2051-2055
    - July 27-31, 1959 (Box 114)
      Week #2056-2060
    - August 3-7, 1959 (Box 114)
      Week #2061-2065
    - August 10-14, 1959 (Box 114)
      Week #2066-2070
    - August 17-21, 1959 (Box 114)
      Week #2071-2075
    - August 24-28, 1959 (Box 114)
      Week #2076-2080
    - August 31 to September 4, 1959 (Box 114)
      Week #2081-2085
    - September 7-11, 1959 (Box 114)
      Week #2086-2090
    - September 14-18, 1959 (Box 114)
      Week #2091-2095
    - September 21-25, 1959 (Box 115)
      Week #2096-2100
    - September 28 to October 2, 1959 (Box 115)
      Week #2101-2105
    - October 5-9, 1959 (Box 115)
      Week #2106-2110
    - October 12-26, 1959 (Box 115)
      Week #2111-2115
    - October 19-23, 1959 (Box 115)
      Week #2116-2120
    - October 26-30, 1959 (Box 115)
      Week #2121-2125
    - November 2-6, 1959 (Box 115)
      Week #2126-2130
    - November 9-13, 1959 (Box 115)
      Week #2131-2135
    - November 16-20, 1959 (Box 115)
      Week #2136-2140
    - November 23-27, 1959 (Box 115)
      Week #2141-2145
    - November 30-to December 4, 1959 (Box 116)
      Week #2146-2150
    - December 7-11, 1959 (Box 116)
      Week #2151-2155
    - December 14-18, 1959 (Box 116)
      Week #2156-2160
    - December 21-25, 1959 (Box 116)
      Week #2161-2165
    - December 21-25, 1959 (Box 116)
    - December 28-31, 1959 (Box 116)
      Week #2166-2169
    - January 1, 4-8, 1960 (Box 116)
      Week #2170-2175
    - January 11-15, 1960 (Box 116)
      Week #2176-2180
    - January 18-22, 1960 (Box 116)
      Week #2181-2185
    - January 25-29, 1960 (Box 116)
      Week #2186-2190
    - February 1-5, 1960 (Box 116)
      Week #2191-2195
    - February 8-12, 1960 (Box 116)
      Week #2196-2200
    - February 15-19, 1960 (Box 117)
      Week #2201-2205
    - February 22-26, 1960 (Box 117)
      Week #2206-2210
    - February 29 to March 4, 1960 (Box 117)
      Week #2211-2215
    - March 7-11, 1960 (Box 117)
      Week #2216-2220
    - March 14-18, 1960 (Box 117)
      Week #2221-2225
    - March 21-25, 1960 (Box 117)
      Week #2226-2230
    - March 28 to April 1, 1960 (Box 117)
      Week #2231-2235
    - April 4-8, 1960 (Box 117)
      Week #2236-2240
    - April 11-15, 1960 (Box 117)
      Week #2241-2245
    - April 18-22, 1960 (Box 118)
      Week #2246-2250
    - April 25-29, 1960 (Box 118)
      Week #2251-2255
    - May 2-6, 1960 (Box 118)
      Week #2256-2260
    - May 9-13, 1960 (Box 118)
      Week #2261-2265
    - May 16-20, 1960 (Box 118)
      Week #2266-2270
    - May 23-27, 1960 (Box 118)
      Week #2271-2275
    - May 30-to June 3, 1960 (Box 118)
      Week #2276-2280
    - June 6-10, 1960 (Box 118)
      Week #2281-2285
    - June 13-17, 1960 (Box 118)
      Week #2286-2290
    - June 20-24, 1960 (Box 119)
      Week #2291-2295
    - June 27 to July 1, 1960 (Box 119)
      Week #2296-2300
    - July 4-8, 1960 (Box 119)
      Week #2301-2305
    - July 11-15, 1960 (Box 119)
      Week #2306-2310
    - July 18-22, 1960 (Box 119)
      Week #2311-2315
    - July 25-29, 1960 (Box 119)
      Week #2316-2320
    - August 1-5, 1960 (Box 119)
      Week #2321-2325
    - August 8-12, 1960 (Box 119)
      Week #2326-2330
    - August 15-19, 1960 (Box 119)
      Week #2331-2335
    - August 22-26, 1960 (Box 120)
      Week #2336-2340
    - August 29 to September 2, 1960 (Box 120)
      Week #2341-2345
    - September 5-9, 1960 (Box 120)
      Week #2346-2350
    - September 12-16, 1960 (Box 120)
      Week #2351-2355
    - September 19-23, 1960 (Box 120)
      Week #2356-2360
    - September 26-30, 1960 (Box 120)
      Week #2361-2365
    - October 3-7, 1960 (Box 120)
      Week #2366-2370
    - October 10-14, 1960 (Box 120)
      Week #2371-2375
    - October 17-21, 1960 (Box 120)
      Week #2376-2380
    - October 24-28, 1960 (Box 121)